+[AI Now!](https://fibery.io/ai)

Solutions

[Feedback  
managementCentralize feedback in one place, link it to features with the help of AI, and close the feedback loop once the feature goes live.](https://fibery.io/feedback-management)

[Facts-based  
prioritizationAggregate customers feedback from many sources, link feedback to features, make smart decisions about priorities, and invent new ideas together](https://fibery.io/prioritization)

[Feature specs  
creationMix work and knowledge. Brainstorm ideas on a whiteboard, write beautiful specs inside features, and create solutions with customers' requests in mind.](https://fibery.io/ideation)

[Roadmapping  
solutionTurn chaotic data into an actionable roadmap. Ensure that your product development efforts are always in sync with customer needs.](https://fibery.io/roadmapping)

Platform

Resources

•••

Solutions

Platform

Resources

Cookie settings

Team

Get a demo

Policies

Privacy Policy

====================

Welcome to Fibery's Privacy Policy, designed to provide clarity on how we handle your data. Our aim is to ensure transparency regarding the information we collect, why we collect it, and how we utilize it. We encourage you to carefully review this policy to understand your rights and options for safeguarding your privacy.

#### History:

Definitions
-----------

* "Fibery," "we," "us," and "our" refer to Fibery, Inc. and relevant affiliates and in this context refers to the entity responsible for managing your information, whether as a Controller or Processor, as detailed further in this document.
* Fibery website, accessible at [www.fibery.io](https://fibery.io/), is denoted as the "Website."
* Fibery Software-as-a-Service Solution, encompassing Fibery workspaces and related functionalities, constitutes the "Services."

Applicability of Privacy Policy
-------------------------------

This Privacy Policy clarifies the handling of your Personal Data in various contexts, including your usage of the Website and Services

It also extends to other engagements you may have with Fibery, such as customer support queries, participation in webinars or user conferences, and sharing feedback, among others.

While the scope of data processing may vary across the mentioned services and websites, this document encompasses the most comprehensive scenarios for clarity and completeness.

**If you do not agree with the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy, you should refrain from accessing or using any of Fibery's Services, websites, or other facets of its business.**

It's important to note that this Privacy Policy specifically excludes any third-party applications or software that may integrate with Fibery's Services via plugins, scripts, or external tools. The organization (such as your employer or another entity) that has entered into the Service Agreement ("Customer") retains control over their instance of the Services ("Instance") and any associated Customer Data.

Should you have inquiries regarding specific Instance settings and privacy practices, please reach out to the Administrator of the Customer whose Instance you are utilizing. If you are a registered Services user, you can find contact information for your Instance Administrator(s) in the "People" view within your Account at https://YOUR-INSTANCE.fibery.io. If you've received an invitation to join an Instance but have yet to create a user account, kindly seek assistance from the Customer that issued the invitation.

Information we receive and collect
----------------------------------

Fibery may collect and receive Customer Data (including Personal Data) and other information and data:

Information you provide to us
-----------------------------

### Account and Profile Information

We collect information about you and your company as you register an Instance, create or modify your user account, make purchases, as well as use, access, or interact with the Services and websites (including but not limited to when you upload, download, collaborate on, or share Content). Information we collect includes:

* Contact information such as full name, email address, **mailing address, and phone number**
* Billing information, including billing addresses, and credit card information, is collected and processed by a third-party payment processor on behalf of Fibery. Fibery does not store or directly process credit card information. The processing of this information is subject to the privacy policy and practices of the third-party payment processor. Please refer to their [privacy policy](https://www.braintreepayments.com/cy/legal/braintree-privacy-policy) for more information on how they handle your data.
* Profile information such as your login, password, profile picture, and **job title**
* Preferences information such as notification and preferences

You may provide this information directly when you enter it in the Service.

In some cases, another user (such as a system Administrator) may create a user account on your behalf and may provide your information, including Personal Data (most commonly when your company requests that you use our Services). We collect Information under the direction of our customers, and usually have no direct relationship with the individuals (Data Subjects) whose personal data we process. If you are providing information (including Personal Data) about someone else, you must have the authority to act for them and to consent to the collection and use of their Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Content

In the course of using our Service or website, we collect and store the content that you create, input, submit, post, upload, transmit, store, or display. This content includes any Personal Data that you opt to include.

### Other submissions

We also gather additional data that you provide to our Website or through participation in interactive features of our Service. This may include engaging in surveys, contests, promotions, activities, events, job applications, requesting customer support, communicating via third-party social media platforms, sharing feedback, or any other form of communication with us. For instance, if you encounter an issue with a Fibery product, you may submit information to our Support Services or post it in our public forums.

Information we collect from your use of the Service and еру website.
--------------------------------------------------------------------

### Web Logs

As with any website and Service delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Website and Service. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type (User Agent), device screen size, URLs of referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, information you search for, locale and language preferences, information about browser configuration and plugins, language preferences and cookie data, identification numbers associated with your Devices (where available), and system configuration information (where available).

### Services Metadata and Analytics

We collect analytics information when you use our Website and Service to help us improve services and optimize our users' experience. In the Service, this analytics information consists of the feature and action of the Service being used, the associated account name, the user ID and IP address of the individual who is using the feature or function, as well as additional information required to detail the operation of the function and which parts of the Service are being used.

Upon request, we connect Personal Data to information gathered in our log files and analytics as necessary to improve Services for individual customers or resolve issues when requested by users. This combined Information is then treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Analytics Information Derived from Customer Data

Analytics information also consists of data we collect as a result of running queries against Data across our user base for the purposes of generating Usage Data. "Usage Data" is aggregated data about a group or category of features or users that does not contain Personal Data or any Confidential Information submitted to the Service. For example, we may query Customer Data to determine the number of Projects created in Accounts or the number of work items created in the Account.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Fibery and third party partners, use various technologies to collect information, such as cookies. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We use cookies to to allow you to access and use the Websites or Service without re-entering your username or password (authentication), improve and customize Services and your User Experience, to count visits, and understand which areas and features of the Website and Service are most popular.

For more details about how we use these technologies, please see our [Cookies Policy](https://fibery.io/cookies-policy).

### Information from third party services

We also obtain information from third parties and combine that with Information we collect through websites. For example, we may have access to certain information from a third party social media or authentication service if you browse our Websites. Any access that we may have to such Information from a third party social or authentication service is in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by that service. You should check your privacy settings on these third party services to understand and change the information sent to us through these services.

### How we use information we collect

Customer Data will be used by Fibery in accordance with Customer instructions, including any applicable terms in the Agreement and Customer use of Services functionality, and as required by applicable law. Fibery is a Processor of Customer Data, and the Customer is the Controller. Customer may, for example, use the Services to grant and remove access to an Instance, assign roles and configure settings, access, modify, export, share, and remove Customer Data, and otherwise use the Services.

We use the Information we collect about you (including Personal Data to the extent applicable) for multiple purposes, including:

* Provide, operate, maintain, improve, prevent, or address service errors, security, or technical issues in Services.
* Enable you to access and use Services, including uploading, downloading, collaborating on, and sharing Content.
* Process and complete transactions, as well as send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices.
* As required by applicable law, legal process, or regulation.
* To send emails and other communications. We may send you service, technical and other administrative emails, messages, and other types of communications. We may also contact you to inform you about changes in our Services, our Services offerings, and important Services-related notices, such as security and payment notices. These communications are considered part of the Services, and you may not opt out of them unless you cancel the service completely.
* In addition, we sometimes send emails about new product features, promotional communications, or other news about Fibery Services and products. These are marketing messages so you can control whether you receive them. You have the ability to opt out of receiving any of these communications upon receiving any of such.
* Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to Services, and other illegal activities.
* Personalize Services and websites, including by providing content, features, or advertisements (for the Websites) that match your interests and preferences.
* Enable you to collaborate, and share Data with users you designate.
* For other purposes for which we specifically obtain your consent.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not use the Personal Data that appears in our Analytics Data or Web logs for any purpose. The use of Information collected through our Services and websites shall be limited to the purposes disclosed in this policy.

If Information is aggregated or de-identified so it is no longer reasonably associated with an identified or identifiable natural person, Fibery may use it for other purposes such as sharing usage statistics in our blogposts. To the extent Information is associated with an identified or identifiable natural person and is protected as Personal Data under applicable data protection laws, it is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Personal Data.”

### Information sharing and disclosure

We will not share or disclose any of your Personal Data or Other Data with third parties except as described in this Policy. We do not sell your Personal Data or other Data.

### Your Use

When you use Fibery Service, Data you have provided will be displayed back to you.

Third Party Services
--------------------

Customer can choose to connect Third Party Services using Apps, scripts or other tools to their instance. Typically, Third Party Services are software that integrate with our Service, and Customer can permit its Instance Users and/or Administrators to enable and disable these integrations for their Instance. Once enabled, the provider of a Third Party Service may share certain information with Fibery. For example, if a Source Control integration is enabled to permit Source code commits to be linked to Fibery Entities in the Instance, we will receive repository access credentials and source code along with additional information that the application has made available to Fibery. Administrators and Users should check the settings and additional details for these Third Party Services to understand what data may be disclosed to Fibery. When a Third Party Service is enabled, Fibery is authorized to connect and access Data made available to Fibery

Generally, no one is under a statutory or contractual obligation to provide any Customer Personal Data or other Data (collectively, “Data”). However, certain Information is collected automatically and, if some Information such as Instance setup details is not provided, we may be unable to provide the Service.

Third Party Service Providers and Partners
------------------------------------------

We may engage third party companies or individuals as service providers or business partners to process Data and support our business. These third parties may, for example, provide server hosting and storage services. Additional information about the the sub-processors we use to support delivery of our Services is available as part of our Data Processing Addendum per request or [here](https://vizydrop-svc.fibery.io/svc/vizydrop/shared/drop/664f10d56162f07adaddea39?authkey=af4774574c627777a9b7). This list may change over time.

Corporate Affiliates
--------------------

Fibery may share Other Information with its corporate affiliates, parents, and/or subsidiaries with such access governed by this Policy in any case.

During a change to Fibery business
----------------------------------

If Fibery engages in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, sale of some or all of Fibery’ assets or stock, financing, public offering of securities, acquisition of all or a portion of our business, a similar transaction or proceeding, or steps in contemplation of such activities (e.g. due diligence), some Data may be shared or transferred, subject to standard confidentiality arrangements and this Policy’s provisions.

Aggregated or obfuscated Data
-----------------------------

We may disclose or use aggregated and/or completely obfuscated Data for any purpose. For example, we may share aggregated or de-identified Other Information with prospects or partners for business or research purposes, such as telling a prospective Fibery customer the average size of the Instance database.

To comply with Law
------------------

If we receive a request for information from a Law Enforcement Agency, we may disclose Data if we reasonably believe disclosure is in accordance with or required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. We will notify you about such a request immediately upon receiving it.

With Consent
------------

Fibery may share Data with third parties when we have consent to do so.

Data Retention
--------------

Fibery will retain Customer Data in accordance with a Customer’s instructions, including any applicable terms in the Terms of Service and as required by applicable law. Fibery may retain Personal Information for Instance Administrators and Owners after you have deactivated your account for the period of time needed for Fibery to pursue legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with (and demonstrate compliance with) legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements — usually for no longer than 6 years. Other Instance Data submitted to the Service will be removed or obfuscated within 6 months after the Service License expiration, unless we're explicitly instructed by the Customer to remove data immediately. To deactivate an organization account, please contact [Supportor Sales](mailto:sales@Fibery.io).

As part of the Fibery's technical solution we are preserving the change history in the AuditLogs. While Fibery retains all change history, specific data in the Audit Log is not subject to recovery according to our internal security policies.

Your Choices
------------

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from Fibery by using the unsubscribe link within each email or emailing us to have your contact information removed from our email list or registration database. Although opt-out requests are usually processed immediately, please allow ten (10) business days for a removal request to be processed. Even after you opt out from receiving any promotional or supporting messages from us, you will continue to receive important technical transactional messages from us regarding Service until your Instance is deactivated or removed.

Security
--------

Fibery takes security of data as our first priority and works hard to protect Information you provide from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access or disclosure. These steps take into account the sensitivity of the Information we collect, process and store, and the current state of technology. To learn more about current practices and policies regarding security and confidentiality of the Services, please see our [Security Statement](https://fibery.io/security). You're also welcome to request additional information about pentests and certificates via email to [Support](mailto:support@fibery.io). Given the nature of communications and information processing technologies, Fibery cannot guarantee that Information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems and services, will be absolutely safe from any intrusion by others.

Age Limitations
---------------

To the extent prohibited by applicable law, Fibery does not allow use of our Service and Website by anyone younger than 16 years old unless there is a custom agreement in place. If you learn that anyone younger than 16 has unlawfully provided us with personal data, please contact us via [new@fibery.io](mailto:new@fibery.io) or [Support](mailto:support@fibery.io), and we will take the necessary steps to delete such information.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

Fibery may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Laws, regulations and industry standards evolve, which may make those changes necessary, or we may make changes to our business. We will post the changes to this page and encourage you to review our Privacy Policy to stay informed. If we make significant changes that alter your privacy rights, Fibery will provide additional notice via email or through the Service. If you disagree with the changes to this Privacy Policy, you should deactivate your Services account.

International data transfers and model clauses

Fibery may transfer your Personal Data to countries other than the one in which you live. We deploy the following safeguards if Fibery transfers Personal Data originating from the European Union or Switzerland to other countries not deemed adequate under applicable data protection law:

* Strict security measures mentioned above as well as in other documents
* European Union Model Clauses and Data Processing Addendum. Fibery offers Data Processing Addendum as well as European Union Model Contractual Clauses, also known as Standard Contractual Clauses, to meet the adequacy and security requirements for our Customers that operate in the European Union, and other international transfers of Customer Data. While protection is provided by default in accordance with GDPR applicability to your Personal Data - you may want to directly sign our standard Data Processing Addendum and Model Clauses as part of Service Purchase process, and we welcome you to request your copy via email at [new@fibery.io](mailto:new@fibery.io) or [Sales](mailto:sales@fibery.io)

Data Controller and Processor definition
----------------------------------------

Data protection law in certain jurisdictions differentiates between the “Controller” and “Processor” of information. In general, the Customer is the Controller of Customer Data. In general, Fibery is the Processor of Customer Data and the Controller of Other Information or individual Leads who just created a Service instance or signed up for information such as a mail list, webinar, etc..

Your rights and updating your information
-----------------------------------------

Individuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their Personal Data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to Information, as well as to seek to access, update, delete, or correct this Information.

Regardless of your country of residence, you can accomplish this using the settings and tools provided in your Instance user account or Customer Center account. If you cannot use the settings and tools, contact your Instance Administrator as mentioned above or our Customer Support via [support@fibery.io](mailto:support@fibery.io) for additional access and assistance.

If your account is managed by an Administrator, that account administrator may have control with regards to how your account information is retained and deleted.

To the extent that Fibery processing of your Personal Data is subject to the GDPR, Fibery relies on its legitimate interests, described above, to process your data. Fibery may also process other Information that constitutes your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes as described above. You have a right to object to Fibery use of your Personal Data for this purpose at any time by opting out; do this by contacting us via[support@fibery.io](mailto:support@fibery.io) or [new@fibery.io](mailto:new@fibery.io)

Data Protection Authority
-------------------------

Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to:

* Restrict Fibery use of Other Information that constitutes your Personal Data
* Raise a question or lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or the Cyprus Data Protection Commissioner, which is Fibery' supervisory authority in the European Union.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area and believe we maintain your Personal Data within the scope of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our supervisory authority:

Office of the Cyprus Commissioner for Personal Data Protection ('Commissioner') br 1, iasonos Str. 2nd Floor, 1082 Nicosia, CyprusP.O.  
BOX 23378, 1682 Nicosia  
T +35722818456  
F +35722304565  

Contacting us
-------------

Please feel free to contact Fibery if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, or if you are seeking to exercise any of your statutory rights. You can contact us at [support@fibery.io](mailto:support@fibery.io) or at our mailing address below:

**28 Oktovriou 2, 1st Floor, Flat/Office 101  
Egkomi, Makedonitissa,2414, Nicosia  
Cyprus**

Last update date: **May 22nd 2024**

Try for free till you 🖤 it, or till trial expires 🤷

A 14-day trial is on us. No credit card required.

Get a demo

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Rated 4.8 on [G2](https://www.g2.com/products/fibery/reviews) and [Capterra](https://www.capterra.com/p/210658/Fibery/#reviews)

Inspired by inventors

[Douglas Engelbart, engineer and inventor](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Douglas_Engelbart)[Bret Victor, interface designer](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bret_Victor)[Alan Kay, computer scientist](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alan_Kay)[Wassily Kandinsky, painter and art theorist](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wassily_Kandinsky)[Margaret Hamilton, software engineer](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Margaret_Hamilton_(software_engineer))[Rich Hickey, creator of Clojure](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clojure)[Edwin Catmull, president of Pixar](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edwin_Catmull)[Benoit Mandelbrot, mathematician](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Benoit_Mandelbrot)[Ada Lovelace, mathematician](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ada_Lovelace)[Richard Feynman, theoretical physicist](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Feynman)[J. C. R. Licklider, psychologist and computer scientist](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/J._C._R._Licklider)[Boris Delaunay, mathematician](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boris_Delaunay)[Georgy Voronoy, mathematician](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgy_Voronoy)

Product discovery & development platform

Rated 4.8 on [G2](https://www.g2.com/products/fibery/reviews) and [Capterra](https://www.capterra.com/p/210658/Fibery/#reviews)[](https://www.g2.com/products/fibery/reviews)[](https://www.capterra.com/p/210658/Fibery/#reviews)

Solutions

Platform

Resources

Cookie settings

Team

© Fibery Limited[Terms](https://fibery.io/terms)[Privacy Policy](https://fibery.io/privacy-policy)[Cookies Policy](https://fibery.io/cookies-policy)
